(Howard:)Hmm.
(Penny(spits out drink explosively. Howard types. Robot arm hands Penny a napkin):)Thank you
for driving me.
(Penny:)You're welcome.
(Sheldon:)I wish you weren't
wearing flip-flops.
(Sheldon:)It's dangerous
to drive in flip-flops.
(Leonard:)Sheldon.
Sorry.
(Sheldon:)I just don't want to be
yet another flip-flop fatality.
(Penny:)Can I ask you
a question?
(Sheldon:)Given your
community college education,
(Sheldon:)I encourage you to ask me
as many as possible.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
Well, my question is--
(Penny:)and I'm pretty sure
I know the answer--
(Penny:)is this your first date?
(Sheldon:)That depends.
(Sheldon:)Does square-dancing
with my sister
(Sheldon:)at a Teens for Jesus
Fourth of July Hoedown
(Sheldon:)count as a date?
(Howard:)No.
(Sheldon:)Then, this is my first date.
(Penny:)Okay. Well, then,
there's a couple of things
(Penny:)you should probably know.
(Sheldon:)I have a master's degree
and two doctorates.
(Sheldon:)The things I should know,
I do know.